welcome back to another shotcut tutorial
欢迎回到另一个截图教程
in this video we're going to be looking
在这段视频中 我们将看到
at transitions and crossfades between
过渡和交叉淡入淡出
different images and also between the
不同的图像 也在
video clips and so I'm gonna drag down
视频片段 所以我要把
first just left click and drag a couple
首先 只需左键单击并拖动几个
of these down into my timeline these are
在我的时间表中 这些是
just a few images and then also we're
只有几张照片 然后我们也
going to do just some video clips here
我在这里只做几个视频剪辑
and I'll resize my video so they're
我会调整我的视频大小 这样他们就
about the same length as the images and
与图像的长度大致相同
I'm leaving just being a little sloppy
我要走了 只是有点马虎
here just leaving some gaps in between
这里只是在两者之间留了一些空隙
that's okay because it actually helps us
这没关系 因为它实际上帮助了我们
illustrate something for these
为这些说明一些东西
transitions so to do a transition what
过渡所以要做什么过渡？
we have to do I'm going to zoom in a
我们必须这样做 我要放大一个
little bit on the timeline to actually
在时间线上一点一点 实际上
do a transition we need to just there's
做一个过渡 我们需要的只是
no filter or something we can add in the
没有过滤器或我们可以添加到
transitions there's no actual transition
过渡没有实际的过渡
to drag and drop on top of a clip or
要将其拖放到剪辑顶部或
something instead what we have to do is
相反 我们要做的是
actually overlap two clips and it'll
实际上重叠了两个片段 它将
create a transition but it's not doing
创造了一个过渡 但它没有做到
it if there's a gap in between it won't
如果两者之间有差距 它就不会
do it because if there's a gap in
这样做是因为如果在
between the program thinks that we're
在节目中认为我们是
trying to move them close together and
试着让它们靠得更近
we're accidentally overlapping a little
我们不小心有一点重叠
bit so it thinks that's an error so we
所以它认为这是个错误 所以我们
have to actually get rid of that gap
必须真正消除这一差距
first so if there's no gap in between
首先 如果两者之间没有差距
and two clips are touching each other
两个夹子相互接触
then we can left-click the clip that's
然后 我们可以左键单击该剪辑
in front and however far we overlap it
在前面 无论我们重叠得多远
it'll create this little cross this
它会创造出这个小十字架
little X and we can that's then like a
小X和我们可以 然后就像一个
little dissolve transition and it's also
小溶解过渡 它也是
an audio Prostate if you have audio so
一个音频前列腺 如果你有音频的话
like these ones I can move this over
像这些一样 我可以把这个移过去
here make them right next to each other
在这里 让它们紧挨着
right now it's just a hard cut from one
现在 这只是一个艰难的削减
to the other the audio is kind of is
对于另一个人来说 音频是一种
kind of a loud hard cut with the audio
声音很大 很硬 声音很大
and the video just cuts over so if we
视频就这样中断了 所以如果我们
drag this one over top again however
然而 将这一条再次拖到顶部
long you want the transition to be maybe
很长时间内你想要的过渡也许是
a really long transition we leave a big
一个非常长的过渡 我们留下了一个很大的
gap there and it will slowly transition
差距在那里 它会慢慢地过渡
to the audio it'll crossfade the audio
对于音频 它会使音频产生交叉衰落
and dissolve the video overtop of it
并将视频溶解在上面
so that's pretty cool if you want to
所以如果你想的话这很酷
make changes to this under properties is
在属性下对其进行更改
where we do that so it's not under
我们这样做的地方 这样它就不会在
filters while the that X transition box
筛选器 同时使用该X转换框
is selected whether or not where the
被选中 无论
playhead is over it but while it's
PlayHead已经过去了 但当它
selected if we click on properties we
如果我们单击我们的属性 则选中
have some different ways we can change
有一些我们可以改变的不同方式
that instead of doing it dissolve we can
与其这样做 我们还可以
do this a barn door horizontal and
这样做是水平的谷仓门 然后
that'll do something different it's like
它会做一些不同的事情 就像
a comes in from the sides we can change
A从我们可以改变的边线进入
it to be like this iris box so we can
它就像这个虹膜盒子 所以我们可以
change different transitions another way
以另一种方式更改不同的过渡
to get rid so now if we move this to
所以现在如果我们把这个移到
it'll move all of it together so at the
它会把所有的东西都放在一起 所以在
clip in front if we move it it actually
如果我们移动它 就把它夹在前面
moves the transition and the clip that
移动过渡和
it's attached to another way to get rid
它依附于另一种摆脱
of the this gap here we can just
在这个缺口上我们可以
right-click and click on remove and now
右键单击 然后单击删除和立即
I'll actually get rid of a gap so we
我真的会消除一个缺口 所以我们
could these ones we can right-click on
我们可以用鼠标右键点击这些吗
the gap here and over remove it and have
这里和上面的缝隙移走了它 并有
like a kind of a ripple delete it this
就像一条涟漪删除它这个
brings everything in all the other clips
带上所有其他剪辑中的所有内容
so now we have no gaps here also to do
所以现在我们在这里也没有差距要做
the transition it has to be the clip in
它必须是其中的剪辑的过渡
front so that if we want to have a
这样 如果我们想要有一个
transition between this image and this
此图像和此图像之间的过渡
image the whatever clip is in front has
想象一下前面的任何剪辑都有
to be overlapped overtop of the one
重叠在一个上面
behind it if we try to overlap the one
如果我们试图把它重叠在一起的话
in front so this one will try and drag
在前面 所以这只会试着拖动
it over top it just it'll just move the
它在上面它只是它只会移动
whole timeline in that direction so we
整个时间线都在那个方向 所以我们
have to drag the one in front overtop of
必须将前面的那个拖到上面
it that makes sense
这就说得通了
so now we have a fade there and fade
所以现在我们有一个淡入淡出的地方
there and again we can change all of
我们可以一次又一次地改变
those this one doesn't have a transition
那些这个没有过渡的
yet this is just a hard cut from the
然而 这只是一个艰难的削减与
picture to the video so we can do this
视频的图片 这样我们就可以这样做了
one too and then this one's the same way
一个也是 然后这个也是一样的
so this one's not gonna have very much
所以这个不会有太多
and then we can just get rid of this by
然后我们就可以通过
right-clicking and going remove that
右键单击并删除该选项
space there now we have a bunch of
太空现在我们有一堆
transitions most of them are gonna be
它们中的大多数都将是
the dissolve there's also some options
解散也有一些选择
for the hardness is like if we want it
因为坚硬就像我们想要的那样
to just how so can we do we can't do on
我们怎样才能做到我们不能做到
that one put like on the vertical bars
那个放在垂直杆上的
the hardness is like if it's a hard line
它的坚硬就像是一条坚硬的线
it will just be like that if we have it
如果我们有了它就会是这样的
all the way down to zero so I guess 100
一直到零 所以我想是100
percent is how how hard and soft it is
百分比是指它有多硬有多软
so this will be a hard line when it's
所以这将是一条强硬的路线 当它
2-0 see it's like a straight line just
2-0看 就像一条直线
cutting down as opposed to being like
减少 而不是像
soft like this so different transitions
像这样的柔软 所以不同的过渡
have different settings you can adjust
具有您可以调整的不同设置
after I think it might just be the
在我认为这可能只是
softness on all of these ones yeah
所有这些都是柔和的是的
anyway so let's change a couple
不管怎样 让我们换几个吧
different will just randomly select a
Different将随机选择一个
few transitions here and I'll change
这里有几个过渡 我会改变的
this one to do that here we have it so
这个在这里做那个 我们有 所以
we'll play and look with our look what
我们会玩耍 看看我们的外表是什么
our project looks like we have some
我们的项目看起来有一些
transitions overlapping we still have
我们仍然有重叠的过渡
our audio but our audio cross fades
我们的音频 但我们的音频交叉褪色
between each clip and that is basically
在每个片段之间 基本上是
it that's using transitions in shot cut
它是在镜头剪辑中使用过渡
hopefully this helped you go ahead and
希望这能帮助你继续前进
might come and subscribe and leave your
可能会来订阅 然后留下你的
questions or comments below if you have
如果您有以下问题或评论
any and I'll catch you in the next video
任何人 我都会在下一个视频中看到你